

354B 2053 Willowbrook Dr., West Lafayette, IN 47906, 440-773-4974, adalipi@purdue.edu

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Purdue Graduate student with a focus in Virtual Reality and Data Visualization at the Computer Graphics Technology program. Has a strong mathematical background and is experienced with data analysis. Is interested in further developing her skills in VR.

SKILLS

- Creative problem solver
- Strong organizational skills
- Microsoft Windows, Office and Excel proficient

- Experience with Maya Animation and OpenGL
- Experience with Unity
- Knowledgeable in C#, Java, and Python

- Experience with SAS, Julia, R and MATLAB
- Basic Video Editing and Photoshop skills
- Experience with HTML and CSS

EXPERIENCE

Virtual Reality Pedestrian-Autonomous Vehicle Interactions Benchmark

March 2020 - Current

Suite Research Member

Purdue University | West Lafayette, IN

- Created a virtually based simulation for pedestrian-AV interactions using Unity and the NAVMESH System.
- In charge of the Traffic and Road System logic.
- Developed interactable UI interfaces for the car models.

Teacher Assistant August 2019 - Current

Purdue University | West Lafayette, IN

- Help students to advance their spatial abilities in order to successfully communicate their engineering ideas using visual techniques.
- Educate students on how to become proficient with CAD software like CATIA and PLM platforms like Aras.

Marshalls Associate April 2017 - July 2019

T.J. Maxx & HomeGoods | Fairview Park, OH

- Greeted and assisted customers.
- Managed different projects.
- Worked independently and on a team.

Space Academy Research Intern

June 2018 - August 2018

NASA Glenn Research Center | Cleveland, OH

- Worked on the Bio-Inspired Solar Electric Propulsion Investigation team.
- Acquired data of hydrophobic and hydrophilic plant structures using scholarly journals.
- Organized and defined variables that affect hydrophobicity using data analysis and Excel.
- Modeled data for optimal hydrophobic surfaces using R studio.
- · Focused on machine learning.

Baldwin Wallace Space University Student

March 2018 - March 2018

Johnson Space Center | Houston, TX

• Spent a week at the Johnson Space Center in Houston.

- Participated in different group projects like rocket building and launching.
- Interacted with NASA employees to learn more about the center and their mission.

Mathematics and Computer Science Tutor

December 2017 - May 2018

Baldwin Wallace University | Berea, OH

- Offered tutoring services to students in different math and computer science subjects.
- Encouraged students to become active learners.
- Offered different learning methods that can be suitable to the student.

High School to Higher Education Course Assistant

September 2016 - December 2016

Baldwin Wallace University | Berea, OH

- Advised and instructed students on tutoring in local high school as part of the Honors Program.
- Monitored the students' work and progress.
- Calculated the students' payments and assisted the teacher with budgeting.
- Distributed and clarified information regarding necessary application forms.

High School to Higher Education Tutor

January 2016 - April 2016

Baldwin Wallace University | Berea, OH

- Tutored high school students in Math and English in Facing History New Tech, downtown Cleveland.
- Addressed issues concerning the students and collaborated with the teacher to improve their learning experience.
- Informed students on different post-secondary education opportunities.

EDUCATION

MS May 2021

Purdue University, West Lafayette, IN

Current GPA: 4.00/4.00

Bachelor of Mathematics May 2019

Minor in Software Engineering

Baldwin Wallace University, Berea, OH

GPA: 3.86/4.00

PSEOP January 2015

Cuyahoga Community College, Cleveland, OH

LANGUAGES

Fluent in Spanish, Albanian and basic Italian.